All right, guys. So, today we have a fun
one. I'm going to be showing you exactly
how we went from zero to over 1.2
million dollars in annual recurring
revenue using pretty much nothing but
LinkedIn. I'm going to give you the
step-by-step system so you can copy
exactly what we've done, but it's not
just going to work for agencies. We're
actually actively managing over 60
clients of B2B consultants, B2B SaaS,
B2B businesses, B2B coaches. [music]
Like, we've done the whole lot and it's
going to work for any B2B business whose
target market is on LinkedIn. We've
obviously been able to scale our agency
to a solid point over the last couple of
years, but we've been able to generate
even more millions in pipeline for our
client and we've helped people go from
pretty much not knowing when their next
client is going to come having to
literally turn down business because of
how much traffic they're getting. And I
think the interesting part is we see so
many industries and we manage so many
profiles and we've found a repeatable
system that's working at a large scale
and we have the best outlook on LinkedIn
as a whole and we know exactly what's
happening behind the curtain is going to
generate leads. And I'm not just talking
about all going viral on the algorithm,
right? That's a part of it, but at the
end of the day we are businesses. We're
not trying to be celebrities. We're not
trying to be influencers. We're trying
to make LinkedIn
>> [music]
>> a profitable marketing channel and
that's exactly what I'm going to show
you how to do in this video. All right,
so I pulled up Miro just so I can show
you the system more in-depth and
essentially the first thing I want to
show you was the actual numbers. So, I
did mention 1.2 million dollars ARR and
that's what we're currently doing, but
we're aiming for a lot higher. I mean,
we've done over 100K month for the last
6 months and we're consistently growing
month-over-month. And I'm going to be
honest, we're aiming for for way higher.
So, these are just very conservative
numbers and we've achieved those results
with only 31K followers, zero dollars
spent on paid ads, and zero cold
outreach messages sent. The fact is that
you can actually do this as well, and
it's sort of unheard of for LinkedIn
content to be a million dollar a year
marketing channel, but you can do this,
too. A really interesting thing is that
the majority of our audience matches our
ICP. Like, we're currently generating, I
guess you could say three to five
dollars per follower, and most people on
LinkedIn, they're generating a dollar,
or maybe they're generating less than a
dollar because they don't actually have
any clients that are coming from
LinkedIn. So, you can definitely achieve
revenue without having a huge audience.
And that's exactly what brings me to the
first idea that I want to get out of you
guys' head. More followers is not more
revenue. The consumer social model is
basically that you should get as many
followers as possible, get as much brand
awareness as possible, go big, go broad,
get 200,000 followers, maybe only 2% of
your actual ICP, but it basically trains
the algorithm to show your content to
people who are never going to buy from
you. And it causes the founders to make
bad decisions which are not incentivized
to the actual growth of the company. The
buyer concentration model is where we
are 90% focused on solely getting the
exact decision makers that we want to
reach. Especially with the way LinkedIn
works now, the more niche you are, it
will actually show you to that specific
ICP. So, they've sort of shifted the
algorithm where it's going to be a lot
more focused on showing you to the right
people rather than, you know, a huge
amount of people. So, here's the three
components that run together. Now, first
of all, we need content that pulls in
buyers. Second of all, we need a profile
that converts that content. And then, we
need two mechanisms to turn engagement
into booked calls. And when you have all
of these three set up, you have the
foundation of a million dollar a year
LinkedIn bond funnel. So, here's the
system breakdown. Section one, I'm going
to show you the actual content that
attracts buyers. So, personal branding
content where we talk about morning
routines, quotes of the day, leadership
lessons, like that generic, you know,
what marriage taught me about B2B sales
is it's a big joke. Like it's a big joke
because it's not authentic, it's not
relevant, and you're genuinely achieving
nothing. Unless you're doing it in a
sarcastic way, but at the same time
that's not going to generate buyers. So,
you can
personal post, but it needs to be
relevant to your ICP. You need to
engineer it that way. So, let me give
you a test. I want you to write a post
or pick a post that you already have
scheduled or you've posted it before and
read through it and just say, can a
qualified prospect that is in a very
specific situation that you help, I want
you to ask yourself if a qualified
prospect can actually resonate with that
post. Do they agree with the situation?
Do they also have the same pain points
that you talked about? Is there
some sort of link? If there's no links
at all, then it's just not targeted. I'm
going to give you two different content
types that actually work. So, named
problem posts is where we name an
expensive problem the ICP's already
thinking about. So, for example, I wrote
a post for a company that was selling AI
voice solutions to home service
companies and what we talked about there
was how home service companies are
losing tens of thousands of dollars a
month because they're not answering
calls, right? They're missing calls,
they're not answering calls during night
time or out of office hours and we
literally just made a post where we
said, "Hey, look, in the hook, this is
how much you're losing, but instead AI
can do it for this price." So, I, you
know, to give you some mock numbers, it
was like home service businesses are are
losing 80K a month on missed calls. AI
can do it for 10K. And the the
interesting thing about that post was
that we literally had our price in the
hook and we got somebody in the comment
to tag one of their partners and that
partner became a client from that post.
And that post only got like, I don't
know, 15 likes, but it got them a client
for 10-16k, I think. That is That is
like the perfect example of having a
super niche specific post where we're
naming the problem, we're clearly
articulating how big the problem is, and
we also clearly show like, "Look, this
is the solution and this is why it makes
sense." It's like, for example, my
clients pay me a few thousand dollars a
month and then I'm generating them many,
many, many more thousands of dollars a
month. It makes sense. It makes sense.
So, having it that way and structuring
it in a way where it's very easy to
understand. Even a stupid person can
look at that and say, "If I pay these
guys 10k to build an AI for me, even if
I'm only getting back 20k a month, it's
still worth it, right?" So, think about
it that way. The next thing is I want to
talk about awareness or like surfaced
problem posts. So, this is where we
surface a problem they didn't know they
have or pain that they haven't named
yet. So, surface a problem is basically
where we're going to say, "Hey, look,
have you ever been in this situation?"
May- Maybe it's like a soft, indirect
sort of hinting at the pain point. So,
one type of post I've seen is like SEO
agencies. What they'll do is they'll
say, "Hey, here's how to audit your SEO
with five steps." And it's like, "Look
at these five different metrics. This is
what it means if each of them are below
average. This is the average. This is
what you can do to fix it." And the fact
is in that case, we're literally giving
them an audit in a LinkedIn post where
if they then go and execute even one of
those steps and they see that their
metrics are below average, what are they
going to do? They're not going to leave
it. And who are they going to go to to
fix it? You, obviously. So, they'll
probably DM you asking like for help or
they'll go to a website, they'll start
learning more about what you do. Imagine
they go through all of those steps and
every single metric is below average and
they realize how much they need help.
So, that's a super strong type of post.
You can do some sort of audit post or
um awareness post in any sort of
industry, and then you can also do a
separate post or in the same post talk
about the fixes to each of those
problems. Now, the compound effect is
the fact that a lot of people do not buy
straight away. Some of them do, some of
them take longer. One right person
follows because you have now, using the
two post types, you've named their exact
situation, the exact ICP that you're
looking for. They're then going to see
pretty much every single one of your
posts for the next 6 months, and that's
why I recommend always posting on the
same days, always posting at the same
time, and always making sure all the
content's relevant because it's going to
build a routine, not just with the
audience, but also with the algorithm,
and it's going to know, "Now we're
expecting a post from him," and it's
genuinely going to push you out more and
more and more. Now, this consistent
presence is going to consistently have
you at the top of this person's mind,
and each post they see is just building
more and more and more and more trust.
And eventually, they're going to read
the case studies, they're going to look
into it. If they aren't already fully
trust you to buy, they will, and then
you're already positioned as the answer
by the time they are. So, it's like it's
it's just the easiest close in the world
as well. You don't need like a crazy
sales sales process or anything like
that because these people are warm.
They've they've done this whole process,
they feel like they know you, you know?
And especially if you're funneling to
maybe other platforms like an email list
or like a YouTube channel, I mean,
you're just going to get even more
nurturing value out of that. And and
this exactly explains how we were able
to scale to over 1.2 million because
30,000 concentrated followers. And the
fact is that not even all of them are
the ICP, the majority are, but not all
of them. So, it's like even less than
30,000 ICP followers, and we've been
able to extract so much revenue out. And
that just shows exactly why we're able
to get the results we have, because
31,000 really
targeted, concentrated followers
produces 10 times more than 300,000 just
completely sparse followers that don't
actually care about your content. And if
you actually post something for the ICP,
then they're not going to listen,
they're not going to like it, you're not
going to get client. Quick note before I
get into the next section. If you want
me to look at your current LinkedIn
setup and show you exactly what we do
for our paid clients, then there will be
a link in the description for you to
check out. I do want to be transparent
and say that this isn't like some free
consulting call. I'm going to give you
my suggestions, but I'm also going to
see if you're fit for our service. So,
please do keep that in mind and let's
get into section two. So, section two is
the funnel. And on LinkedIn, your funnel
is your LinkedIn profile. There's four
profile elements that you need to have
built out. So, number one, job title as
the headline. I see this way too often.
People say, "CEO at company you've never
heard of." Like, genuinely, I understand
that you want to position yourself as
"Oh, look, I'm the owner." The truth is
everyone's a CEO. Anyone can say that
you're a CEO on your profile. Like, and
it almost makes people put you into that
same bucket as everyone else. I would
honestly remove your job title
completely, and I would focus much more
on essentially the outcome. So, talking
about who you help, specifically.
Because a lot of people they have these
generic headlines, they're not even
calling out to an ICP. In my headline,
the first two words are agencies and
SaaS. That's the first two words. Who do
you think is going to click my profile?
Agencies and SaaS. Who's my ICP?
Agencies and SaaS. Like, it's genuinely
it's not rocket science, it's just about
clarity, okay? So, the second thing is
they have custom button links that link
to a generic homepage, or they just
don't have them at all. Like, are we
like there is people which you might not
even have content, but people are
searching up and you people will go to
your profile just through connections,
just through search, and they're able to
book calls with you because you do not
have it as an option. Like, how are we
supposed to book calls if it's not an
option? So, you need to set up a custom
button link to your actual landing page,
okay? I would recommend either to a
calendar or to a landing page if it's
optimized, that's fine as well. Most
people don't even have a featured
section. That's the third mistake. Most
section, but it's actually one of the
most powerful nurturing tools that you
can use, and essentially you would use a
case study, you would have a video
testimonial, and then maybe you would
have a valuable like methodology
breakdown. The profile as a whole is
necessary for you to generate leads, but
I would argue that it also affects the
perception. So, even from the content,
people will see your profile picture,
your name, and the start of your
headline. If it just looks like, you
know, completely it looks AI, if it
looks fake, if it just looks cheap, what
are people going to think when they see
your post, right? Like, if that's their
first impression, they they're obviously
not going to trust you or see you as an
authority. So, you'll you basically want
to give yourself a head start and
position yourself from the get-go as the
top authority as possible. The other
thing I wanted to mention is often like
people have, you know, in their about
section or in their experience section,
it's just kind of like generic career
history.
I think you can include career history,
but you need to have tie it to be
relevant. Like, oh, I worked in this
company with these big names. Okay,
that's more authority. Or, oh, I worked
here and we worked on these specific
things. That's another thing. Like, you
sort of need to think about is this
actually relevant to the ISP? The same
thing you ask with all those posts, you
ask it with each line that you're
writing in your profile. Now, there is
actually a really big silent leak that
founders don't diagnose, and that's the
fact that some people have amazing
reach. And maybe this is you. Maybe you
have amazing reach, or maybe not even
amazing, but if you're getting 10,000
impressions a month, 50,000 impressions
a month, you should still be getting a
few leads a month from LinkedIn.
The issue is that often you get all that
traffic, you never see the people who
visited, and you never see the people
who were about to call with you, but
they can't or they just don't, right? It
doesn't resonate. So, what happens is
founders essentially assume, wait,
content my content's not good enough. I
need to get more reach. I need to get
more reach. But, what's what happens is
you're actively just losing more and
more money by doing that because you're
pouring traffic into a leaky bucket.
Section three is the two conversion
mechanisms. I actually haven't talked
about this in many other videos, so I'm
pretty excited, but essentially you need
to convert all this traffic and go out
of your way a little bit to do the most
you can to make the most out of it,
right? If we want to extract the maximum
value out of LinkedIn, we don't need to
do cold outreach, but we're more focused
on doing this warm, targeted outreach to
people who've already shown some sort of
interest, right? So, you know, most
people don't even have great content or
a clean profile, but if you did have a
great content and a clean profile, you'd
actually still be leaving a lot of money
on the table just by simply not having
this in place to extract more leads out
of the same engagement that you're
getting. So, mechanism one is for the
lead magnet post. So, most people post
and they just wait for DMs, whereas with
a lead magnet post, we essentially tell
people to comment a certain word and
then send a connection request so we can
message them, and we essentially offer
some sort of freebie to send to them.
This could be a free resource, this
could be, you know, a free trial for
your software, this could be a free
audit, could be whatever it is, right?
Every commenter is going to then become
a first-degree connection who sees
everything posted going forward cuz
that's just how it works. They literally
become followers. They automatically
That's how LinkedIn works. It's it's
amazing. It's working in your favor. And
these aren't random followers because
with lead magnets, if you position it
correctly, these are people who have
raised their hand for the exact problem
that you solve. And each new connection
increases the net the reach of the next
post, right? Cuz we with a lead magnet,
if you get 500 comments, you might get
400, 300 followers. I mean, from one
post, that's absurd. And then you bet
you best believe that stacks on top of
each other. And then you mix it in with
all the types of posts and I mean, it's
just going to be you're going to be
flooded with leads. Mechanism two is
profile views. Now, profile views is
probably the highest intent you can get
without direct engagement. These are
people who've seen your profile. It's
like website visitors, but for LinkedIn.
Maybe these people have even visited
your website, right? But essentially, if
people have visited your profile or they
visited it multiple times, that is
active research and that is buying
behavior. Most people do not even look
at their profile views analytics, but
this is genuinely the lowest hanging
fruit you can use to engage. So, usually
you want to do one genuine question. So,
I would recommend sort of playing into
the profile view idea. Say something
like, "Hey, LinkedIn told me you were
snooping around my profile and I was
wondering if there's anything I can help
you with?" Question mark. "I'm happy to
point you in the right direction or
provide any advice if it's relevant."
Right? Something like that. I think
soft. I think just trying to figure out
what is their intent, right? Are they
interested in your services? Are they
having a certain pain point? This stage
is sort of an info gathering stage. We
need to figure out where are they at.
Okay? And usually your response rate on
these is going to be pretty high. I
mean, probably 20 to 50% depending on
how good your profile and your content
is. And the fact is, these people are
already warm. Like, it's it's just it's
going to be way better than any sort of
cold outreach you could ever do. Here's
exactly why this compounds. So,
these three layers, it's pretty obvious,
right? But we get content that pulls in
the right people.
We then get a profile which holds those
right people. and then we get mechanisms
to force conversations and booked
meetings with the people that our
profile has captured. And also, I just
want to say something. 31,000 followers
is a lot, right, with this method. It's
a lot. You could still start getting
leads from LinkedIn at 5,000, 2,000. You
know, we've had people with 200
followers booked seven qualified calls
in a matter of days. Like, do you need
to build the funnel before the audience
feels big enough? Like, there's no harm
in selling. If you're offering a
genuinely valuable service, and then
you're putting out genuinely valuable
content, there is absolutely no harm in
selling. And one thing I think that most
people miss, and I really want to make
it clear, is that yes, I have 31,000
followers, but I was getting leads way
before this. Like, even when I had 1,000
followers, even when I had 5,000
followers, I was generating leads from
LinkedIn. Like, I think there is a lot
of people on LinkedIn that you don't
really hear about often, but they have
10,000 followers, and it's a 50k a month
or 100k a month marketing channel for
them. Like, you should start selling
before the audience like feels big
enough. I think that's one of the
biggest lies that people say is build
the audience first. It's like, if you're
selling a genuinely valuable service,
and your content is genuinely valuable,
you should have absolutely no problem
selling your service. So, I would say
get this up and running as soon as
possible, otherwise you're going to
wish, you know, you started sooner. So,
if you do actually want to work with us
and get my direct help on LinkedIn, then
please book a call with me in the link
in the description.